Local embedding unavailable ([WinError 126] The specified module could not be found. Error loading "D:\Sourcecode\vinai\lab\lab5\lab5\Lib\site-packages\torch\lib\shm.dll" or one of its dependencies.); using mock embeddings.
Embedding backend: mock embeddings fallback
Documents: 8
Chunks loaded: 53
Note: mock embeddings are deterministic but do not encode semantic meaning.

=== Query 1: Số suất và giá trị Green Tech ===
Học bổng Green Tech 2026 có bao nhiêu suất, giá trị bao nhiêu và kéo dài bao lâu?
TOP-3:
  1. score=0.241365 doc=usth-green-tech-scholarship-2026 id=usth-green-tech-scholarship-2026#0
     # Green Tech Scholarship and Internship 2026  An opportunity to gain hands-on internship experience while receiving a scholarship at GREEN IN – a pioneer in green transition and Net Zero solutions 🌱  ## Scholarship Value  04 scholarships | 
  2. score=0.239625 doc=usth-financial-aid-2024-2025 id=usth-financial-aid-2024-2025#11
     USTH hopes that with scholarships and financial support from the University, partners, and benefactors, students will continue to make every effort to overcome challenges, pursue knowledge, and shine in the future.
  3. score=0.238837 doc=usth-vallet-scholarship-2026 id=usth-vallet-scholarship-2026#2
     Chỉ tiêu phân bổ (Khối Đại học): 15 suất chính thức và 05 suất dự bị. (Riêng bậc Cao học và Nghiên cứu sinh sẽ thực hiện xét duyệt trực tuyến độc lập tại hệ thống website của Ban Điều hành).  ## II. Đối Tượng Và Tiêu Chuẩn Xét Chọn  Ứng viê
Gold markers found in top-3: ['18,000,000', '6 months'] / ['18,000,000', '6 months']

=== Query 2: Mốc thời gian Green Tech ===
Hạn cuối nộp hồ sơ học bổng Green Tech 2026 là ngày nào và thời gian dự kiến bắt đầu là khi nào?
TOP-3:
  1. score=0.278959 doc=usth-scholarship-application-2026 id=usth-scholarship-application-2026#2
     Seed of Talent Scholarship (SOT)  Access Scholarship (AS)  For detailed eligibility criteria and scholarship values, please refer to the Scholarship Regulations for the academic year 2026–2027.  II. Eligibility Requirements and Scholarship 
  2. score=0.196530 doc=usth-scholarship-procedure id=usth-scholarship-procedure#1
     Step 2: prepare proposed lists for scholarship and financial support; organize the SFA council and issue a final decision.  Within 15 days after the accepting deadline for students’ applications and proposals of Departments, the Student Ser
  3. score=0.169679 doc=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026 id=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026#1
     Nhà trường thông báo về việc tiếp nhận hồ sơ đăng ký học bổng năm học 2025-2026 đối với sinh viên, học viên và nghiên cứu sinh đang học tại trường như sau:  ## Đối tượng và tiêu chí nộp học bổng  1.1. Học bổng khuyến khích học tập (MS):  – 
Gold markers found in top-3: [] / ['March 23, 2026', 'April 2026']

=== Query 3: Quy trình ===
Quy trình xét học bổng và hỗ trợ tài chính của USTH gồm những bước nào?
TOP-3:
  1. score=0.254554 doc=usth-scholarship-regulation-2026 id=usth-scholarship-regulation-2026#0
     # Regulations on Scholarship for USTH Students  The University of Science and Technology of Hanoi would like to announce Decision No.177/QĐ-ĐHKHCNHN dated March 12th, 2026 on issuing scholarship regulations for USTH students.  This regulati
  2. score=0.248296 doc=usth-scholarship-application-2026 id=usth-scholarship-application-2026#0
     # Scholarship Application Submission 2026-2027 Wave 1  Announcement On Scholarship Application Submission, Academic year 2026–2027 (wave 1)  In the academic year 2026–2027, the University of Science and Technology of Hanoi (USTH) plans to a
  3. score=0.246322 doc=usth-financial-aid-2024-2025 id=usth-financial-aid-2024-2025#4
     Attending the ceremony, representatives from Vietcombank included Mr. Tran Hai Dang, Deputy Director of Vietcombank Thang Long Branch, and Ms. Nguyen Thi Xuan Hoa, Head of Khuc Thua Du Transaction Office. Representing USTH were Ms. Pham Thi
Gold markers found in top-3: [] / ['Step 1', 'Step 2', 'Step 3']

=== Query 4: Quỹ học bổng 2026-2027 ===
Trong năm học 2026-2027, USTH dự kiến dành bao nhiêu tiền cho quỹ học bổng và áp dụng cho những nhóm người học nào?
TOP-3:
  1. score=0.302896 doc=usth-financial-aid-2024-2025 id=usth-financial-aid-2024-2025#10
     At the ceremony, Hai shared that he was deeply moved and grateful to receive full tuition support for the 2024–2025 academic year from the University and donors. This meaningful support not only eased his financial worries but also served a
  2. score=0.293903 doc=usth-financial-aid-2024-2025 id=usth-financial-aid-2024-2025#2
     In addition, with the educational philosophy of “leaving no student behind,” and with the support of generous donors and compassionate partners, USTH provides hardship scholarships and financial aid to students in difficult circumstances. T
  3. score=0.249903 doc=usth-scholarship-procedure id=usth-scholarship-procedure#2
     In November, the Student Services Department and related departments are responsible for widely public the decision and list of students granted scholarships and financial aid support.  Scholarships and financial support will be bank-transf
Gold markers found in top-3: [] / ['VND 16 billion', 'undergraduate']

=== Query 5: Đối tượng quy định 2026 ===
Đối tượng sinh viên nào được áp dụng các quy định học bổng năm 2026 của USTH?
FILTERED:
  1. score=0.217508 doc=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026 id=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026#8
     – Đối với trường hợp em thấy điểm/ số tín chỉ trên ERP chưa đúng, vui lòng tự điền điểm chính xác (báo lại với Khoa chuyên môn để được cập nhật điểm chính xác trên hệ thống). Bên cạnh điểm các em điền/ ERP tự điền, phòng CTSV cũng sẽ trao đ
  2. score=0.192965 doc=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026 id=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026#1
     Nhà trường thông báo về việc tiếp nhận hồ sơ đăng ký học bổng năm học 2025-2026 đối với sinh viên, học viên và nghiên cứu sinh đang học tại trường như sau:  ## Đối tượng và tiêu chí nộp học bổng  1.1. Học bổng khuyến khích học tập (MS):  – 
  3. score=0.189933 doc=usth-scholarship-application-2026 id=usth-scholarship-application-2026#3
     Students receiving Talent Scholarships (except full scholarships) will automatically be considered for Merit Scholarships or SFI Scholarships with corresponding bonus points based on their achievements.  If a student meets the conditions fo
Gold markers found in top-3: [] / ['Vietnamese students', 'international students']
UNFILTERED (A/B comparison):
  1. score=0.301341 doc=usth-scholarship-procedure id=usth-scholarship-procedure#0
  2. score=0.217508 doc=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026 id=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026#8
  3. score=0.192965 doc=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026 id=usth-current-student-scholarship-2025-2026#1

